Guide to the AFSCME, Local 420, Hospital Workers Photographs PHOTOS.212
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Color Prints
  - Subseries C: Local 420
    - Sub-subseries viii: Local Officers
      - Butler, James and Sarah Kennedy Honored by Morris Brown College, undated (Box 13, Folder 661)
      - Kennedy, Sarah, undated (Box 13, Folder 662)
      - [Santiago, Aurora's Birthday Party in New Orleans], undated (Box 13, Folder 663)
    - Sub-subseries ix: Meetings
      - Town Hall Meeting Healthcare Senator Paterson, Feb 17, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 664)
      - ["AFSCME Council 79" Meeting], undated (Box 13, Folder 665)
      - [Miscellaneous 420 Meetings -- Dates Unknown], undated (Box 13, Folder 666)
      - Shortage of Staff & Job Freeze, undated (Box 13, Folder 667)
      - Union Officials Meeting, undated (Box 13, Folder 668)
    - Sub-subseries x: Personalities
      - Mother Annie Williams (including her funeral in May 2000), undated (Box 13, Folder 669)
    - Sub-subseries xi: Political
      - [Rally for Michael Dukakis in Memorial Baptist Church and at Harlem Hospital; probably 1988] (Box 13, Folder 670)
      - [Sharpton for US Senate], 1994 (Box 13, Folder 671)
      - Ruth [Messinger] for Mayor Harlem Hospital, Oct 9, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 672)
      - Ruth [Messinger] for Mayor City Hall, Oct 24, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 673)
      - Endorses Hon. Gregory Meeks, Jan 22, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 674)
      - 420 for P[eter] Vallone for Governor, Oct 8, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 675)
      - Count Every Vote Campaign (Florida, [George W.] Bush Election) [Probably 2000], Jun 22, 1905 (Box 13, Folder 676)
      - [Political Gatherings -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 13, Folder 677)
      - [Politicians -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 13, Folder 678)
      - [Reelect State Senator Efrain Gonzalez Jr.], undated (Box 13, Folder 679)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries a: General
      - Rally Bellevue [Hospital], Jun 4, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 681)
      - Bellevue [Hospital Rally], Oct 26, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 682)
      - [Bellevue Hospital -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 13, Folder 683)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries c: Bronx Municipal Hospital
      - Bronx Municipal See The Light Bronx Urban League Awards Ceremony, undated (Box 13, Folder 684)
      - Red Bag Checks Victory Bronx Municipal, undated (Box 13, Folder 685)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries d: Brooklyn Central Laundry
      - B[rooklyn] C[entral] L[aundry Rally], Apr 27, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 686)
      - Brooklyn Central Laundry [Rally], Jun 11, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 687)
      - Brooklyn Central Laundry [undated Rallies] (Box 13, Folder 688)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries f: Coney Island Hospital
      - [Coney Island Hospital Community Meeting], Mar 9, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 689)
      - Coney Island Hospital Rally, Jul 1, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 690)
      - Coney Island Rally Church, Jan 29, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 691)
      - Coney Island 54 Rally, Jan 28, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 692)
      - Coney Island 54 City Hall, Feb 19, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 693)
      - Coney Island Rally, Nov 6, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 694)
      - Coney Island 54 [Rally], undated (Box 14, Folder 695)
      - Coney Island Rally (Burger King), undated (Box 14, Folder 696)
      - [Coney Island Rally (Burger King) -- Autumn], undated (Box 14, Folder 697)
      - [Coney Island Hospital Victory Meeting], undated (Box 14, Folder 698)
      - [Coney Island Hospital -- WEP "Workfare" Rally], undated (Box 14, Folder 699)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries h: Elmhurst Hospital
      - McDonald's Out!!! Elmhurst Hospital, Mar 5, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 700)
      - Elmhurst Health and Hospitals Corporation Hearing, Oct 30, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 701)
      - Elmhurst Rally, Dec 24, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 702)
      - [Elmhurst Hearing], Jan 22, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 703)
      - Cosme, Gloria -- Retire[ment from Elmhurst Hospital] 346 B'way, Mar 17, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 704)
      - Elmhurst Rally [Re-Open Employee Cafeteria], undated (Box 14, Folder 705)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries k: Harlem Hospital
      - Zonzie Moore Harlem Hospital, Jan 5, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 706)
      - Housekeepers Week Harlem Hospital (9-13-94 -- 9-16-94), Sep 13, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 707)
      - All Night Vigil Harlem Hospital, May 15, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 708)
      - D[octors] Support Harlem Hospital, Apr 28, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 709)
      - Harlem Hospital Rally [Columbia University], May 20, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 710)
      - Harlem Hospital Rally, Jul 8, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 711)
      - Rally Harlem Hospital, Jul 21, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 712)
      - No Lay Offs (Rally) Harlem Hospital [Sarah Kennedy], Jan 23, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 713)
      - ["Harlem Hospital Beds" Meeting], undated (Box 14, Folder 714)
      - Harlem Hospital Center, undated (Box 14, Folder 715)
      - [Harlem Hospital Demonstration with the "Union Rat"], undated (Box 14, Folder 716)
      - [Harlem Hospital -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 14, Folder 717)
      - [Harlem Hospital No Layoffs Demonstration], undated (Box 14, Folder 718)
      - Harlem Hospital Rally, undated (Box 14, Folder 719)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries l: Jacobi Medical Center
      - Jacobi Hospital [Rally], Feb 12, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 720)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries n: Lincoln Hospital
      - Open Lincoln AIDS Ward [Demonstration], Mar 29, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 721)
      - Lincoln Hospital "Opening of 27 Bed AIDS Unit", 1991 (Box 14, Folder 722)
      - Lincoln Housekeepers Day, Sep 24, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 723)
      - 27 AIDS Bed Unit [Lincoln Hospital], undated (Box 14, Folder 724)
      - [Lincoln Hospital -- An Awards Ceremony], undated (Box 14, Folder 725)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries o: Metropolitan Hospital
      - Met Rally (Metropolitan Hospital) [No McDonald's], Oct 27, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 726)
      - Employee Lounge Met[ropolitan Hospital?], Sep 23, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 727)
      - [Metropolitan Hospital Center -- No McDonald's Rally], undated (Box 14, Folder 728)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries p: Neponsit Hospital
      - Rally City Hall Park Save Neponsit, Oct 7, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 729)
      - Press Conference Health and Hospitals Corporation with Mark Green [(Neponsit Hospital)], Oct 29, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 730)
      - (Neponsit) Victory Rally, Nov 4, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 731)
      - Giuliani (Rally on Privatization Neponsit Central Laundry Fast Food), undated (Box 14, Folder 732)
      - Neponsit [Rally], undated (Box 14, Folder 733)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries q: North Central Bronx Hospital
      - Henry Wapple Retire [North Central Bronx], Jun 19, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 734)
      - North Central Bronx Hospital [Rally], Apr 20, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 735)
      - North Central Bronx [Rally], May 12, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 736)
      - North Central Bronx Not for Sale Rally, Jul 15, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 737)
      - City Hall Hearing North Central Bronx, Aug 10, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 738)
      - North Central Bronx [Hospital] (Rally), Nov 17, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 739)
      - [Demonstration to Save North Central Bronx Hospital (raining)], undated (Box 14, Folder 740)
      - [Demonstration to Save North Central Bronx Hospital (sun is shining)], undated (Box 14, Folder 741)
      - North Central Bronx Hospital [Rally], undated (Box 14, Folder 742)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries s: Queens General Hospital
      - Queen Hospital Center Rally, Mar 14, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 743)
      - Queens General HHC Hearing, Feb 25, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 744)
      - Queens [Hospital] Rally No McDonald's, Jun 26, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 745)
    - Sub-subseries xiv:Other Organizations, Sub-sub-subseries b: Coalition of Black Trade Unionists
      - [CBTU 24th Annual National Convention (5-25-95 - 5-29-95)], May 25, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 746)
      - CBTU [25th Anniversary] Convention (5-23-96 -- 5-27-96), May 23, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 747)
      - CBTU [Labor and the Minority Community Conference], May 28, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 748)
      - CBTU "The Time is Now" Campaign, May 1999 (Box 14, Folder 749)
      - [CBTU Conference -- Coalition Solidarity], undated (Box 14, Folder 750)
      - [CBTU Conference -- The Black Worker: "Meeting the Challenges of the 90's"], undated (Box 14, Folder 751)
      - [CBTU Meeting? At Omni Shoreham Hotel in Washington, D.C.], undated (Box 14, Folder 752)
      - [CBTU -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 14, Folder 753)
    - Sub-subseries xiv:Other Organizations, Sub-sub-subseries c: Coalition of Labor Union Women
      - [CLUW Honor President Butler], Oct 31, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 754)
    - Sub-subseries xiv:Other Organizations, Sub-sub-subseries h: Transport Workers Union of America
      - TWU [Transport Workers Union of America] Honors Pres. Butler, May 8, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 755)
      - TWU [Transport Workers Union of America] Rally, Dec 8, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 756)
- Series III: Black and White Negatives
  - Subseries C: Local 420
    - Sub-subseries i: General
      - [Early 420 History. See folder #27 for some matching prints.], undated (Box 15, Folder 757)
      - [Early 420 History -- Includes scenes of possible physical conflict and police at DC37 headquarters], undated (Box 15, Folder 758)
      - [Miscellaneous -- Unidentified and Unknown], undated (Box 15, Folder 759)
    - Sub-subseries iv: Demonstrations and Rallies
      - WEP ["Workfare"] Worker Rally City Hall [See Folder #79 for some matching prints.], Jan 15, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 760)
      - Apartheid [See Folder # 100 for some matching prints.], undated (Box 15, Folder 761)
    - Sub-subseries v: Events
      - WEP ["Workfare"] Workers [Press Conference? On the Steps of City Hall?; Meeting Same Day?] [See Folder # 146 for some matching prints.], Oct 7, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 762)
    - Sub-subseries viii: Local Officers
      - [Butler, James and Mayor David Dinkins], undated (Box 15, Folder 763)
      - Chapman, Freida at International Labor Press Association's Convention (Florida) [See Folder #223 for some matching prints.], 1983 (Box 15, Folder 764)
    - Sub-subseries xi: Political
      - Register to Vote Campaign [See Folder #307 for some matching prints.], undated (Box 15, Folder 765)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries b: Bellevue Hospital
      - 420 Bellevue Hospital OR, Jan 5, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 766)
      - 420 C[hief] M[edical] E[xaminer] Office (Bellevue), Mar 20, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 767)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries d: Brooklyn Central Laundry
      - [Brooklyn Central Laundry is Not for Sale Rally.] [See Folder # 344 for some matching prints.], undated (Box 15, Folder 768)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries e: Coler-Goldwater Hospital
      - [Ruth White] Coler Demonstration [at 125th st.], Jun 26, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 769)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries f: Coney Island Hospital
      - Coney Island Rally [See Folder # 366 for some matching prints.], Mar 9, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 770)
      - Coney Island [Hospital Rally] [See Folder # 367 for some matching prints.], Jul 1, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 771)
      - [Coney Island Hospital Rally -- Stop Murdering Public Hospitals] [See Folder #384 for some matching prints.], undated (Box 15, Folder 772)
      - Coney Island [Rally] [See Folder #380 for some matching prints.], undated (Box 15, Folder 773)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries k: Harlem Hospital
      - Harlem [Hospital] Graduation [See Folder #415 for some matching prints.], Mar 24, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 774)
      - Harlem Hosp[ital] Retirement Naomi Trent [Spring 1986] (Box 15, Folder 775)
    - Sub-subseries xiii: Worksite
      - [Hospital Workers -- includes graduation?, member at work, and portrait], undated (Box 15, Folder 776)
    - Sub-subseries xiv: Other Organizations, Sub-sub-subseries b: Coalition of Black Trade Unionists
      - L[ocal 420] CBTU C.U. Mason (negatives), undated (Box 15, Folder 777)
    - Sub-subseries xiv: Other Organizations, Sub-sub-subseries c: Coalition of Labor Union Women
      - CLUW (04/29/82 -- 05/01/82) [Convention] [See Folder #567 for some matching prints.], Apr 29, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 778)
    - Sub-subseries xiv: Other Organizations, Sub-sub-subseries e: National Association for the Advancement of Colored People
      - NAACP Voter Registration Hanover County, VA (8/19/84 - 9/1/84), Aug 19, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 779)
- Series IV: Color Negatives
  - Subseries C: Local 420
    - Sub-subseries iv: Demonstrations and Rallies
      - AFSCME & Local 420 [Support Mushroom Farmers] [See Folder # 98 for some matching prints.], undated (Box 15, Folder 780)
      - Labor Rally in Church [See Folder #609 for some matching prints.], undated (Box 15, Folder 781)
    - Sub-subseries vii: International Friendships
      - Bermuda Industrial Union 50th Year Anniversary [See Folder # 646 for some matching prints.], undated (Box 15, Folder 782)
    - Sub-subseries xiv: Other Organizations, Sub-sub-subseries b: Coalition of Black Trade Unionists
      - [CBTU Miscellaneous] [See Folder # 564 for some matching prints.], undated (Box 15, Folder 783)
- Series V: Color Transparencies, Subseries C: Local 420, Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries u: Sydenham Hospital
  - [Save Sydenham Hospital Demonstration], undated (Box 15, Folder 784)
- Series VI: Color Slides
  - Subseries A: AFSCME
    - [AFSCME Conventions -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 16, Folder 785)
    - [AFSCME Election Campaigns], undated (Box 16, Folder 786)
    - [AFSCME Women Equal Partners Conference and Banquet], undated (Box 16, Folder 787)
    - International Convention in Las Vegas, undated (Box 16, Folder 788)
    - [AFSCME Convention in Las Vegas (?)], Jul 1978 (Box 16, Folder 789)
    - AFSCME Convention in Hawaii, Jul 1978 (Box 16, Folder 790)
    - AFSCME Convention Vote Wurf/Lucy, Jun 1980 (Box 16, Folder 791)
    - Atlantic City AFSCME Convention folder 1, Jun 12, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 792)
    - Atlantic City AFSCME Convention folder 2, Jun 12, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 793)
    - [AFSCME 26th International Convention-- folder 1 of 2], Jun 1984 (Box 16, Folder 794)
    - [AFSCME 26th International Convention -- folder 2 of 2], Jun 1984 (Box 16, Folder 795)
  - Subseries C: Local 420
    - Sub-subseries i: General
      - [Unidentified, Unknown], undated (Box 16, Folder 796)
      - [Voices of 420 Choir -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 16, Folder 797)
      - Voices of 420 Sings at 140 Park Place DC37, Nov 1983 (Box 16, Folder 798)
      - [Voices of 420] Choir in Alabama, Jan 1984 (Box 16, Folder 799)
      - [Voices of 420 Choir in Concert at Lincoln Hospital]], Feb 1984 (Box 16, Folder 800)
      - [Local 420 Members (?) Portraits] [ca. early 1980s], 1980-1990 (Box 16, Folder 801)
    - Sub-subseries ii: Celebrations
      - [Grouped Miscellaneous Celebrations], undated (Box 16, Folder 802)
      - [Miscellaneous Celebrations], undated (Box 16, Folder 803)
      - [P.E.O.P.L.E. Award Ceremony], undated (Box 17, Folder 804)
      - Local 420 During Black History Month, undated (Box 17, Folder 805)
    - Sub-subseries iv: Demonstrations and Rallies
      - [Local 420 Demonstrations in Support of Local 1199], undated (Box 17, Folder 806)
      - [undated, Miscellaneous Demonstrations and Rallies--folder 1 of 2] (Box 17, Folder 807)
      - [undated, Miscellaneous Demonstrations and Rallies--folder 2 of 2] (Box 17, Folder 808)
      - Local 420 [Supports] Columbia [University] Students [in Protest Against Apartheid], undated (Box 17, Folder 809)
      - [Dated, Miscellaneous Demonstration and Rallies-- folder 1 of 5], ca.1980-1985 (Box 17, Folder 810)
      - [Dated, Miscellaneous Demonstration and Rallies--folder 2 of 5], ca.1980 (Box 17, Folder 811)
      - [Dated, Miscellaneous Demonstration and Rallies-- folder 3 of 5], ca.1980 (Box 17, Folder 812)
      - [Dated, Miscellaneous Demonstration and Rallies-- folder 4 of 5], ca.1980 (Box 17, Folder 813)
      - [Dated, Miscellaneous Demonstration and Rallies-- folder 5 of 5], ca.1980 (Box 17, Folder 814)
      - [Rally on the Steps of City Hall], Oct 1981 (Box 17, Folder 815)
      - Memphis, Tenn. [-- Martin Luther King March], 1983 (Box 17, Folder 816)
      - Eleanor Bumpers [Demonstration to Investigate her Murder; probably 1984] (Box 17, Folder 817)
      - [Anti-Apartheid Rally/March in Washington, D.C.], May 1985 (Box 17, Folder 818)
      - [Anti-Apartheid March], Apr 1986 (Box 17, Folder 819)
      - [Local 420 Supports Farm Workers, Jul 1986 (Box 17, Folder 820)
      - [Anti-]Crack Rally in Queens, Sep 6, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 821)
    - Sub-subseries v: Events, Sub-sub-subseries a: General
      - [Cruise/AFL-CIO Convention], undated (Box 18, Folder 822)
      - [Turkey Days -- Miscellaneous and undated] (Box 18, Folder 823)
      - MLK/Memphis and Atlanta [pre- November 1983], ca.1980-1983 (Box 18, Folder 824)
      - Atlanta -- Martin Luther King Jr., Feb 1981 (Box 18, Folder 825)
      - Licensed Practicing Nurse (LPN) Course, Jul 1982 (Box 18, Folder 826)
      - Casandra Lyons Fashion Show in Honor of James Butler, May 1984 (Box 18, Folder 827)
      - [Employee Recognition Day], May 1985 (Box 18, Folder 828)
    - Sub-subseries v: Events, Sub-sub-subseries b: Charity
      - Concert for Ethiopia at Memorial Baptist Church, undated (Box 18, Folder 829)
    - Sub-subseries vi: Hearings
      - [Hearings and Press Conferences], undated (Box 18, Folder 830)
    - Sub-subseries vii: International Friendship/Solidarity
      - [Trip to Africa (?)], undated (Box 18, Folder 831)
      - [Trip to Jerusalem], Aug 1977 (Box 18, Folder 832)
    - Sub-subseries viii: Local Officers
      - [Elect Butler (?) Gathering], undated (Box 18, Folder 833)
      - [Local 420 Officers and Staff (?)], undated (Box 18, Folder 834)
    - Sub-subseries ix: Meetings
      - [Conference at the Ramada O'Hare Inn]], undated (Box 18, Folder 835)
      - Executive Board [Meeting], undated (Box 18, Folder 836)
      - [Meetings -- Grouped Miscellaneous ca.1980s-- folder 1 of 3], ca.1980-1989 (Box 18, Folder 837)
      - [Meetings -- Grouped Miscellaneous ca.1980s-- folder 2 of 3], ca.1980-1989 (Box 18, Folder 838)
      - [Meetings -- Grouped Miscellaneous ca.1980s-- folder 3 of 3], ca.1980-1989 (Box 18, Folder 839)
      - [Meetings -- Miscellaneous ca.1980s], ca.1980-1989 (Box 18, Folder 840)
      - Executive Board [Meeting] Atlantic City, Oct 1981 (Box 18, Folder 841)
      - [A Meeting], Feb 1982 (Box 18, Folder 842)
      - [A Meeting], Apr 1982 (Box 18, Folder 843)
      - [Conference at the Sheraton Centre in New York], Nov 1984 (Box 18, Folder 844)
      - Shop Steward Conference at the Friar Tuck Inn May 9-12, 1985--folder 1 of 2], May 1985 (Box 19, Folder 845)
      - Shop Steward Conference at the Friar Tuck Inn May 9-12, 1985--folder 2 of 3], May 1985 (Box 19, Folder 846)
    - Sub-subseries xiv: Other Organizations, Sub-sub-subseries b: Coalition of Black Trade Unionists
      - [CBTU: "The Black Worker" Conference, Chicago], undated (Box 19, Folder 847)
      - CBTU [Meeting in] Chicago], undated (Box 19, Folder 848)
      - Voices of Local 420 Choir CBTU Ohio, undated (Box 19, Folder 849)
      - CBTU Convention [Memphis] 5/26-5/31/1982, May 1982 (Box 19, Folder 850)
      - [A Banquet -- CBTU], Jun 1983 (Box 19, Folder 851)
      - [Voices of 420 Choir -- CBTU -- Elect Charles Hayes], Jun 1983 (Box 19, Folder 852)
      - [NAACP Overground Railroad March from Richmond, VA to NY, NY 8/19/84-9/1/84], Aug 19, 1984-Sep 1, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 853)
    - Sub-subseries xiv: Other Organizations, Sub-sub-subseries f: National Urban League
      - [National Urban League Annual Conference], 1978 (Box 19, Folder 854)
    - Sub-subseries xi: Political
      - [Badillo, Herman], undated (Box 19, Folder 855)
      - [Barbaro, Frank], undated (Box 19, Folder 856)
      - [Cuomo, Mario], undated (Box 19, Folder 857)
      - [Dinkins, David], undated (Box 19, Folder 858)
      - [Jackson, Jesse], undated (Box 19, Folder 859)
      - [McCall, Carl], undated (Box 19, Folder 860)
      - [Political Events -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 19, Folder 861)
      - [Towns, Edward], undated (Box 19, Folder 862)
      - [Local 420 Supports Carter-Mondale Campaign], Oct 1980 (Box 19, Folder 863)
      - [Voter Registration], May 1982, undated (Box 19, Folder 864)
      - Voter Registration [and March to elect] Mondale-Ferraro, Nov 1984 (Box 19, Folder 865)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries a: General
      - [Hospital Exteriors], undated (Box 19, Folder 866)
      - Nurses Aides Workshop, undated (Box 19, Folder 867)
      - Nurses Aides Workshop [at DC37 Headquarters], undated (Box 19, Folder 868)
      - [Nurses Aides Graduation], Nov 1981 (Box 19, Folder 869)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries d: Brooklyn Central Laundry
      - Brooklyn Central Laundry Meeting, Jun 1983 (Box 20, Folder 870)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries e: Coler-Goldwater Hospital
      - Bird S. Coler [Hospital] Demonstration (Loeb) Management Unfair to Workers, Nov 1981 (Box 20, Folder 871)
      - Demonstration at Goldwater [Hospital] for Parking Spaces/[No Shuttling Employees to Work], undated (Box 20, Folder 872)
      - Goldwater [Hospital] Nurses Aides Meeting, undated (Box 20, Folder 873)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries f: Coney Island Hospital
      - [Coney Island Hospital Rally], Sep 1986 (Box 20, Folder 874)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries h: Elmhurst Hospital
      - Slides on Mr. Carlos Viamonte Local 420 Member Elmhurst Hospital Worker who was stuck in the hand with a needle used on an AIDS patient [Shot by Bill Moore], undated (Box 20, Folder 875)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries o: Metropolitan Hospital
      - Metropolitan [Hospital] HKA [Housekeeping] Meeting, undated (Box 20, Folder 876)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries r: North General Hospital
      - Rally to Save North General Hospital, undated (Box 20, Folder 877)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries s: Queens General Hospital
      - [Rally at Queens General Hospital], undated (Box 20, Folder 878)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries u: Sydenham Hospital
      - [Sydenham Hospital Demonstration], Mar 1980 (Box 20, Folder 879)
      - [Save Sydenham Hospital Demonstration], Sep 1980 (Box 20, Folder 880)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries v: Woodhull Hospital
      - [Demonstration at] Woodhull Hospital [to] Put Workers Back to Work [February, year unknown], undated (Box 20, Folder 881)
      - [Woodhull Hospital Event], Feb 1985 (Box 20, Folder 882)
    - Sub-subseries xiii: Worksite
      - [Worksite -- Laboratory], undated (Box 20, Folder 883)
- Series VII: Oversized mounted photographs
  - Oversize - #s OV-1 through OV-43 (19 ¾ x 13 inches), undated (Box OV, Folder 1-43)
  - Oversize - #s OV-44 through OV-96 (16 x 20 inches), undated (Box OV, Folder 44-96)
  - Oversize - #s OV-97 through OV-100 (24 x 16 inches), undated (Box 21, Folder 97-100)
  - Oversize - #s OV -101 through OV-110 (23 ¾ x 17 ¼ inches), undated (Box 21, Folder 101-110)
  - Oversize - #s OV-111 through OV-133 (20 x 24 inches), undated (Box 22, Folder 111-115, Box 23, Folder 116-120, Box 24, Folder 121-133)
  - Oversize - #s OV-134 through OV-179 (20 x 30 inches), undated (Box 25, Folder 134-146, Box 26, Folder 147-157, Box 27, Folder 158-168, Box 28, Folder 169-179)
  - Oversize - Unnumbered, undated (Box 29, Box 30, Box 31)
  - OV Unprocessed (Box OV3, Box OV4, Box OV5, Box OV6, Box OV7, Box OV8, Box OV9, Box OV10, Box OV22)
- Unprocessed